Finding Aid for Jeffrey R. Parsons papers, 1960-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Archaeological Sites and Projects 1966-2010
  - Zumpango 1973
    - Site Reports
      - Zu-LT-88 (M) III-L13-3C-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-LT-89 (M) III-L13-3D-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-LT-90 (M) III-L13-3D-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-LT-91 (M) I-L11-66B-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-1 (M) II-L2-5B-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-2 (M) II-L2-5B-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-3 (M) II-L2-5B-NE & NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-4 (M) II-L2-5D-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-5 (M) II-L2-5D-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-6 (M) II-L2-5D-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-7 (M) II-L2-3D-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-8 (M) II-l2-5D-NE II-L2-3B-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-9 (M) II-l2-3B-NE II-L2-3A-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-10 (M) II-L2-3A-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-11 (M) II-L2-3D-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-12 (M) II-L2-3D-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-13 (M) II-L2-1B-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-14 (M) II-L2-3D-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-15 (M) II-L2-1B-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-16 (M) II-L2-1B-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-17 (M) II-L2-1B-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-18 (M) II-L2-1B-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-19 (M) Zu-A3-20 II-L2-1B-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-21 (M) II-L2-1B-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-22 (M) II-L2-1B-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-23 (M) II-L2-1B-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-24 (M) II-L2-3A-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-25 (M) II-L2-3C-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-26 (M) II-L2-3C-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-27 (M) II-L21A-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-28 (M) II-L2-1A-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-29 (M) II-L2-1A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-30 (M) II-L2-1A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-31 (M) II-L2-1A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-32 (M) II-L2-1A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-33 (M) II-L2-1A-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-34 (M) IIL2-1A-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-35 (M) II-L2-3B-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-36 (M) II-L5-29B-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-37 (M) II-L5-29B-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-38 (M) II-L5-29B-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-39 (M) II-L2-3D-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-40 (M) II-L2-1A-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-41 (M) II-L5-26B-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-42 (M) II-L5-26B-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-43 (M) II-L5-26B-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-44 (M) II-L5-24C-NE SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A2-45 (MP) II-L5-24D-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-46 (M) II-L5-29C-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-47 (M) II-L5-29C-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-48 (M) II-L5-29C-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-49 (M) II-L5-29C-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-50 (M) II-L5-29C-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-A3-51 (M) II-L5-29C-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-52 (M) II-L5-29C-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-53 (M) II-L5-29C-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-54 (M) I-L8-62C-SW Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-55 (M) I-L8-62C-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-56 (MP) I-L8-62C-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-58 (M) I-L8-62C-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-59 (M) I-L8-62C-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-60 (M) I-L8-62C-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-61 (M) II-L5-29D-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-62 (M) II-L5-29D-NC Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-63 (M) II-L5-29D-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-64 (M) II-L5-29D-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-65 (M) II-L5-29D-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-66 (M) II-L5-29A-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-67 (M) II-L5-29A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-68 (M) II-L5-29A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-69 (M) II-L5-29A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-70 (MP) II-L5-26C-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-71 (MP) II-L5-26A-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-72 (M) I-L8-62A-NW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-73 (MP) I-L8-62A-NW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-74 (M) I-L8-62A-NW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-75 (M) I-L8-62A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-76 (M) I-L8-62A-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-77 (M) I-L8-62B-NW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-78 (M) I-L8-62B-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-79 (M) I-L8-62B-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-80 (M) I-L8-62B-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-81 (M) I-L8-62D-SW Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-82 (M) I-L8-62D-SW (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-83 (M) I-L10-1E-SE I-L10-1F-NE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-84 (M) I-L8-62D-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-85 (M) I-L8-62D-SW Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-86 (M) I-L10-1F-NE Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-87 (M) I-L8-62D-North Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-88 (M) I-L11-64A-NE Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-89 (M) I-L11-64A-NE Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-90 (M) Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-91 (M) I-L11-64D-SE Zumpango West 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-92 (M) I-L10-1B-NE -1D-SW SW -1C-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-93 (M) I-L12-6B-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-94 (M) I-L12-6B-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-95 (M) I-42-6B-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-96 (MP) I-L14-7A-NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-97 (M) II-L8-26B-NW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-98 (M) II-L8-26B-NE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-99 (M) II-L8-26A-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-100 (M) II-L8-26B-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-101 (M) II-L9-4D-NE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-10 (M) II-L9-4D-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-103 (M) II-L11-42A-NW & SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-104 (M) II-L11-42B-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-105 (M) II-L11-42B-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-106 (M) II-L11-42B-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-107 (M) II-L11-42B-SE & NE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-108 (M) II-L11-42B-NE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-109 (M) II-L11-42B-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-110 (M) II-L11-42D-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-111 (M) II-L11-42D-SW Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-112 (M) II-L11-42D-SE Zumpango West (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-113 (M) III-L13-3C-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-114 (M) III-l13-3C-SE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-115 (M) III-L13-3D-SW Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zu-Az-116 (M) I-L11-66B-NE Zumpango West MHP 1973 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 General and Miscellaneous Photos (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Photo Indices Roll1 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 2 All labeled with old site nos. (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 3 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 4 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 5 all labeled with old site nos. (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 6 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 7 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 8 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 9 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 10 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 11 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 12 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 13 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 14 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 15 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 16 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 17 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 18 (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 19 All Pepe's Spindle Whorls (Box 23)
      - Zumpango 1973 Roll 20 (Box 23)
    - Field Notebooks
      - Zumpango Pottery-Chapingo 2007 (Box 23)
      - Jeffrey Parsons, Book 1 & 2 1973 (Box 23)
      - Mary Parsons, Book 1 & 2 1973 (Box 24)
      - Mary Parsons, Book 1 Photos 1973 (Box 24)
    - Map Materials
      - 1973 Survey Airphoto Indices (Box 24)
      - La Selva Lacandona y Tierras Colindantes Chiapas Mexico1953 (Box 24)
      - Caminos de Chiapas 1971 (Box 24)
  - Mexico Ceramic Surveys
    The Mexico Ceramic Surveys, 1967 - 1973 subseries (1.5 linear feet) includes ceramic profiles & descriptions of ceramic materials from the Teotihuacán Valley, Texcoco Region and Chalco.
    - Chalco Ceramic Tabulations 1969 (Box 48)
    - Ixtapalapa (L), 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Aztec Survey Teotihuacán Valley (Box 48)
    - T-A-81 Samples / Completed Surface Samples Teotihuacan Valley Aztec Survey 1966, 1978, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Teotihuacan Valley Aztec Survey Pottery Tabulations (Eva II) 1978, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Teotihuacan Valley -- Sherd Analyses / Aztec Surface Samples -- completed Surface Samples 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Texcoco 1988 (Box 48)
    - Texcoco Strip I 1967, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Texcoco Strip II 1967, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Texcoco Strip III 1967, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Completed Survey Strip III (Box 49)
    - Profiles & Description B/O Upright-Rim Basin (Box 49)
    - Profiles & Description B/O Upright-Rim Bowl (Box 49)
    - Profiles & Description W/R; Y/R; B&W & Y/R; B7 Y/R; P&B&W/O; P/W; B&R/B (Box 49)
    - Profiles & Description Plain Red (Box 49)
    - Profiles & Description B/R (Box 49)
    - Profiles & Description Polychrome (B&W/R) (Box 49)
    - Miniature Vessels Profiles & Description (Box 49)
    - Profiles & Description Comals (Box 49)
    - Undecorated Ware: Jars (Box 49)
  - Ethnographic Field Research
    - Mexico
      The Ethnographic Field Research 1980 -- 1992, sub series, (0.5 linear feet) is made up of field notes, mostly in the form of profiles and description documents of maguey utilization and salt-making in Mexico. Ethnographic research data is focused on the regions of Chimalhuacán, Nexquipayac, and Orizabita. Detailed data about such data is also found in twelve field notebooks included here.
      - Salt-Making Ethnography 1967 (Box 49)
      - Otomi Ethnography -- Mexico 1984 [includes tape transcriptions], 2 volumes (Box 49)
      - Orizabita Fieldnotes -- Otomi Fieldwork 1983, 1984, 2 volumes (Box 49)
      - Orizabita Fieldnotes 1986, 2 volumes (Box 49)
      - Orizabita-Photos & Notes 1986 (Box 49)
      - Orizabita -- Airphoto 1969 (Box 49)
      - Mexico 1987, 2 volumes (Box 49)
      - Nexquipayac -- Photos, Negatives & notes 1987 (Box 49)
      - Nexquipayac -- Field Notes 1988, 2 volumes (Box 49)
      - Nexquipayac -- Field Notes 1988, 1 volumes (Box 49)
      - Mexico 1988 black-and-white photos Nexquipayac (Box 49)
      - SN Workshop, Nexquipayac Mexico 1988 Figures (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Study 1992, 1 volumes (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan -- Contact Prints 1992 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Photos of Insect Categories 1992-1993 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Photos Roll 1 1992 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Photos Roll 2 1992 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Photos Roll 3 1992 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Photos Roll 4 1992 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Photos Roll 5 1992 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Museum Photos 1992 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacan Photos Roll 11 1988 (Box 49)
      - Chimalhuacán Photos -- Model T with balsa (bugs chapter 5 plates) (Box 49)
      - Mexico 1980, 1981 Mexico 1981, 1982 Misc Info 1983, 1983 Photo Record, 2 volumes (Box 49)
      - Photo Record Mexico 1982 Mexico 1984 & 1986, 2 volumes (Box 50)
      - Mexico Photos 1984, 1986 (Box 50)
      - Mexico Photographic Record 1983 (Box 50)
  - Peru 1996-2010
    The Peru subseries 1966-2010 (5 linear feet), is comprised of materials from Parson's survey research in Peru, in the Upper Mantaro Region and the Junin Department. The content is divided into three groupings: Peru, Junin Survey and Wanka Survey material. Documents are, for the most part, survey materials and field notes for the Junin and Wanka Surveys, with specific documentation on Junin, Tarma, Jauja, and Huancayo. Additional material includes indices, classifications, reports, and other research material. These surveys, and thus the majority of the content, date from 1975 to 1976. However, this subseries does have a small number of research material and ceramic inventories, ranging from 2004 to 2010, related to the earlier research.
    - Peru - General
      - Tarma/ Junin Survey Classifications (Box 50)
      - Junin & Tarma Ceramic Analyses & Tabulations 1989 (Box 50)
      - Ridged Fields in Junin Puna-Map of well-preserved samples (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous: Lima Ceramic Material, Re-Study of 75-76 Collections, Notes (Box 50)
      - Hastings -- Maps, Index & Graphs (Box 50)
      - Hastings Sites Tarma 1975 & Huasahuasi 1976, 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Hastings-Site Classification (Box 50)
      - Hastings -- Supplementary Surveys 1980 (Box 50)
      - Ta-Li-53(H) Special Survey August 6, 1980 (Box 50)
      - Overall Survey Areas, 19875 -- 1980 (Box 50)
      - INC Informe -- Maps & Field Number 1980 (Box 50)
      - Sherd Profiles -- Upper Mantaro -- Virginia Pelaez Ocampo (Box 50)
      - Upper Mantaro 1975-1976 Sherd Profiles (Box 50)
      - Upper Mantaro Survey -- Location of Material [Key] (Box 50)
      - Dillehay, Tom -- Chillan Valley ceramics (Box 50)
      - Tarma 1975 (Parsons) Indices (Box 50)
      - Huasahuasi 1976 (Hastings) Indices (Box 50)
      - Provisional Ceramic Evaluations (Tarma) (Box 50)
      - Informe 1977 Prehispanic Settlement Patterns Report 1976 Season -- Upper Mantaro (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous Photos -- Huasahuasi,1976 (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous Photos -- Tarma 1975 (Box 50)
      - Tarma 1975 Site Tracings from Air Photos -- All Scales (Box 50)
      - Junin 1976 Site Tracings & Miscellaneous (Box 50)
      - Upper Mantaro Working Maps & Lists 1980 (Box 50)
      - Tarma 1975 Site-Unit-Featur-Collection; Indices (H); Hastings (Box 50)
      - Indices & Miscellaneous Junin 1976 (Parsons) (Box 50)
      - Junin 1976 Indices TK (Box 50)
      - Site Indices-Huasahuasi 1976 (Hastings) (Box 50)
      - Site Report Formats (Box 50)
      - Junin Puna Photos (Box 50)
      - Santa Valley Peru photograph-- Section of Great Wall -- Shippee Johnson flight circa 1930 (Box 50)
      - Peru Photos 2008 (Box 50)
      - Peru Maps (Box 50)
      - NW Argentina & South America [maps] (Box 50)
      - Site 298 (Box 50)
      - Peru -- Sattelite Image showing Junin, Puna (Box 50)
    - Junin Survey
      - Jun-EI-1(P) Unit 128-P Junin 1976 30884-NW Site 304 (Box 50)
      - Jun-EI-2(P) Unit 135-P Junin 1976 40055-SE Site 312 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-1(P) Coll 304-P Junin 1976 21452-SW Site 231 marcacocha (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-2(P) Coll 305-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 233 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-3(P) Coll 306-P Junin 1976 12185-SW Site 318 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-4(P) Coll 307-P Junin 1976 12185-NW Site 344 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-5(P) Coll 308-P Junin 1976 12185-SW Site 345 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-6(P) Coll 309-P Junin 1976 12185-SW Site 319 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-7(P) Coll 310-P, 311-P Junin 1976 12185-SW Site 320 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-8(P) Unit 126-P Junin 1976 30884-NE Site 166 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-9(P) Unit 127-P Junin 1976 30884-NW Site 302 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-10(P) Coll 312-P Junin 1976 30884-NW Site 301 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-11(P) Coll 313-P Junin 1976 30878-NW Site 55 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-12(P) Unit 132-P Junin 1976 21450-SE Site 240 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-13(P) Coll 314-P Junin 1976 21450-SE Site 59 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-14(P) Unit 133-P Coll317-P, 318-P Junin 1976 12181-NW Site 322 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-15(P) Coll 319-P Junin 1976 12181-NW Site 333 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-16(P) Unit 134-P Junin 1976 40057-NE Site 313 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-17(P) Jun-EI-2(P) Unit 135-P Junin 1976 40055-SE Site 312 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-18(P) Unit 136-P Junin 1976 40057-NE Site 305 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LH-1(P) Fea. 55-P Junin 1976 30878-NW Site 56 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LH-2(P) Fea. 56-P, 57-P, 58-P, 59-P Junin 1976 21450-NE Site 60, 61, 62 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LH-3(P) Unit 129-P Junin 1976 21450-NE Site 60,61,62 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LH-4(P) Unit 130-P Junin 1976 21450-NE Site 60,61,62 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LH-5(P) Fea 60-P, 61-P Junin 1976 21450-SE/NE Site 60, 61, 62 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LH-6(P) Fea 62-P Junin 1976 40057-NE Site 305-A (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-1(P) Coll 300-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 234 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-2(P) Coll 301-P Junin 1976 21452-NE Site 237 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-3(P) Coll302-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 235 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-4(P) Coll 303-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 230 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-5(P) Unit 125-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 229 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-6(P) Fea 38-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 228 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-7(P) Fea 39-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 228 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-8(P) Fea 40-P Junin 1976 21452-SE Site 228-A (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-9(P) Fea 41-P Junin 1976 21452-SW Site 232 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-10(P) Fea 42-P Junin 1976 21452-SW Site 241 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-11(P) Fea 37-P Junin 1976 21452-NE Site 238 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-12(P) Fea 43-P Junin 1976 40051-SW Site 236 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-13(P) Fea 44-P Junin 1976 40051-SW Site 227 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-14(P) Fea 45-P Junin 1976 40051-SW Site 223 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-15(P) Fea 46-P Junin 1976 40051-SW Site 222 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-16(P) Fea 47-P Junin 1976 40051-NE Site 242 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-17(P) Fea 48-P Junin 1976 12185-NE Site 317 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-18(P) Fea 49-P Junin 1976 12185-NE Site 215 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-19(P) Fea 50-P Junin 1976 12185-NE Site 342 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-20(P) Fea 51-P Junin 1976 12185-NW Site 343 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-21(P) Fea 52-P Junin 1976 12185-SW Site 343 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-22(P) Fea 53-P Junin 1976 30884-NW Site 303 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-23(P) Fea 54-P Junin 1976 30884-NW Site 304-A (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-24(P) Unit 131-P Junin 1976 21450-SE Site 239 (Box 50)
      - Jun-?-25(P) Coll 320-P Junin 1976 40047-NE Site 66 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-1(TK) Unit 1-TK Junin 1976 21456-NW Site 201 (Box 50)
      - Jun-LI-2(TK) Fea 1-TK Junin 1976 21454-SW Site 209 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-3(TK) Coll 1-TK Junin 1976 21456-SE Site 310 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-04(TK) Unit 2-TK Junin 1976 21456-SW Site 307 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-05(TK) Feature 11-TK Junin 1976 21454-SE Site 193 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-6(TK) Unit 6-TK Junin 1976 21456-NW Site 315 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-7(TK) Unit 7-TK Junin 1976 21456-SW Site 311 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-8(TK) Fea 16-TK Junin 1976 21454-SE Site 194 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-9(TK) Unit 9-TK Junin 1976 40053-SE Site 213 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-10(TK) Unit 11-TK Junin 1976 40053-SW Site 316 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-11(TK) Unit 13-TK Junin 1976 40053-NE Site 211 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-12(TK) Unit 14-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 212 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-13(TK) Unit 16-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 219 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-14(TK) Coll2-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 220 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-15(TK) Unit 17-TK Junin 1976 12183-NE Site 323 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-16(TK) Unit 18-TK Junin 1976 12183-NW Site 321 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-18(TK) Unit 21-TK Junin 1976 12183-SW Site 337 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-17(TK) Unit 19-TK Junin 1976 12183-NW Site 322 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-19(TK) Unit 22-TK Junin 1976 12183-SW Site 334 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-20(TK) Unit 25-TK Junin 1976 12183-NW Site 341 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-21(TK) Unit 26-TK Junin 1976 12183-NW Site 338 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-22(TK) Unit 27-TK Junin 1976 30882-NW Site 172 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-23(TK) Unit 28-TK Junin 1976 30882-NE Site 171 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-24(TK) Unit 30-TK Junin 1976 30880-SW Site 186 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-25(TK) Coll 4-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW Site 180 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-26(TK) Unit 31-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW Site 176 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-27(TK) Coll 5-TK Junin 1976 30880-NE Site-178 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-28(TK) Unit 32-TK Junin 1976 30880-NE Site 177 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-29(TK) Unit 33-TK Junin 1976 30880-NE Site 174 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-30(TK) Unit 36-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW Site 181 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-31(TK) Unit 37-TK Junin 1976 30875-SE Site 57-58 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-32(TK) Coll 8-TK Junin 1976 30873-SW Site 63 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-33(TK) Coll 9-TK Junin 1976 30873-SW Site 64 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-34(TK) Coll 10-TK Junin 1976 21448-NW Site 65 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-35(TK) Coll 11-TK, 12-TK Junin 1976 12181-NW Site 330, 331 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-36(TK) Coll 13-TK Junin 1976 12181-NE Site 329 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-37(TK) Coll 14-TK Junin 1976 12181-NE Site 327 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LI-38(TK) Unit 38-TK Junin 1976 12181-NE Site 328 (Box 51)
      - Jun-LH-1(TK) Unit 39-TK Junin 1976 30880-NW Site 183-184 Colcas (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-1(TK) Fea 2-TK Junin 1976 21456-SE Site 308 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-2(TK) Fea 3-TK Junin 1976 21456-SW Site 309 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-3(TK) Fea 4-TK Junin 1976 21456-NW Site 306 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-4(TK) Unit 3-TK Junin 1976 21456-NW Site 179 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-5(TK) Fea 5-TK Junin 1976 24156-NW Site 204 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-6(TK) Unit 4-TK Junin 1976 24156-NW Site 205 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-7(TK) Unit 5-TK Junin 1976 21456-NE Site 198-199 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-8(TK) Fea 6-TK Junin 1976 21456-NE Site 200 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-9(TK) Fea 7-TK Junin 1976 21454-SE Site 195 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-10(TK) Fea 8-TK Junin 1976 21454-SE Site 191 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-11(TK) Fea 9-TK Junin 1976 21454-SE Site 192 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-12(TK) Fea 10-TK Junin 1976 21454-NE Site 190 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-13(TK) Fea 12-TK Junin 1976 24156-NW Site 206 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-14(TK) Fea 13-TK Junin 1976 21456-NW Site 207 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-15(TK) Fea 14-TK Junin 1976 21456-NW Site 202 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-16(TK) Fea 15-TK Junin 1976 21456-NE Site 197 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-17(TK) Fea 17-TK Junin 1976 21456-NE Site 196 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-18(TK) Unit 8-TK Junin 1976 30882-NW Site 173 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-19(TK) Unit 10-TK Junin 1976 40053-NE Site 208 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-20(TK) Unit 12-TK Junin 1976 40053-SW Site 214 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-21(TK) Fea 18-TK Junin 1976 40053-NE Site 210 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-22(TK) Unit 15-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 216 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-23(TK) Fea 19-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 217 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-24(TK) Fea 20-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 221 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-25(TK) Fea 21-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 218 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-26(TK) Fea 22-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 225 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-27(TK) Fea 23-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 224 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-28(TK) Fea 24-TK Junin 1976 40053-NW Site 226 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-29(TK) Fea 25-TK Junin 1976 21456-SW Site 314 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-30(TK) Fea 26-TK Junin 1976 12183-SE Site 324 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-31(TK) Unit 20-TK Junin 1976 12183-SE Site 325 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-32(TK) Fea 27-TK Junin 1976 12183-SE Site 326 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-33(TK) Fea 28-TK Junin 1976 12183-SW Site 335 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-34(TK) Fea 29-TK Junin 1976 12183-SW Site 336 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-35(TK) Fea 30-TK Junin 1976 12183-NW (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-36(TK) Unit 23-TK Junin 1976 12183-NW Site 340 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-37(TK) Unit 24-TK Junin 1976 12183-NW Site 339 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-38(TK) Unit 29-TK Junin 1976 30882-SE Site 167 (Box 51)
      - Jun-?-39(TK) Unit 34-TK Junin 1976 30880-NE Site 175 (Box 51)